Guide to the Parents, Families and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG) records, 1972-2009.
Parents, Families and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG) records
- Series X. Media
  - National Press Clippings (misc.), n.d. (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - PFLAG Palm Springs Publicity Packet Sample, 1995 (Box 68, Folder 23)
- Series XI. Photographs
  - PFLAG Pictures 1995-2001 from Binder, 1995-2001 (Box 69, Folder 1-14)
  - PFLAG Pictures 1996-2000 from Binder, 1996-2000 (Box 69, Folder 15-67)
  - PFLAG Pictures (2000) from Binder, 2000 (Box 69, Folder 68-99)
  - 1997 Conference Photographs (including Pro-Disney Rally) from Binder, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 100-126)
  - PFLAGpole Photos Fall 2004 from Binder, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 127-130)
  - PFLAG National Scholarship Winners 2003 from Binder, 2003 (Box 69, Folder 131-133)
  - President Clinton-PFLAG Press Photos, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 134)
  - PFLAG Photos - Early to Mid-1990s - Member-Submitted Photos from Binder, 1990s (Box 69, Folder 135-155)
  - PFLAG Pictures California Conference late 1990s from Binder, 1990s (Box 69, Folder 156-183)
  - PFLAG Pictures (2000 and earlier) Conferences and API Family Project from Binder, ca. 2000 (Box 70, Folder 1-64)
  - PFLAG Pride Rallies from Binder, ca 1990 (Box 69, Folder 65-80)
  - PFLAG Events Photos from Binder, ca 1990 (Box 69, Folder 81-102)
  - Awards Photos from Binder, ca 1990 (Box 69, Folder 103-104)
  - Protest Rallies Photos from Binder, ca 1990 (Box 69, Folder 105)
SEPARATED MATERIAL
Publications Removed From Collection 7616 - To Be Cataloged As Individual Books And Serials In The Human Sexuality Collection:
AIDS Services Directory, 1990, New York State Department of Social Services
AIDS Treatment News, Issue Numbers: 112, 115, 116, 119, 135, 137-139, 143-148, 150-158, 160, 172; Special Report: Essential HIV Consumer Reading; Edición Especial en Espñaol Octubre 1990; Treatment Issues: Volume 5, Number 6; Volume 6, Numbers 1, 3-7
Alternative Family Magazine, River Forest, IL. 1 issue.
And God Loves Each One
Between the Lines, Farmington, MI. 1 issue.
Bravo Bulletin, Columbus, OH. 1 issue.
Connecticut Resource Guide: Lesbian, Gay, and Bisexual Issues in Education. 1997.
Empathy, Volume 2, Number 2
GLPGI Network, Newsletter of the Gay and Lesbian Parents Coalition International, Summer 1993
Helpline/Frontline, Volume One, Number One; Volume One, Number Two
Impact, Volume 18, September 24-October 7, 1993
Justice for All, Equality Illinois. 1 issue.
Little Black Book, Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund, Inc.
National Community AIDS Partnership Annual Reports: 1990-1991; 1991-1992
Federation of PFLAG Newsletter, 13 issues.
Our Daughters and Sons: Questions and Answers for Parents of Gay, Lesbian and Bisexual People, P-FLAG, 1995
P-FLAGpole, 78 issues
The FLAGPOLE of P-FLAG of Metropolitan, Washington, February 1995
Read This Before Coming Out To Your Parents: A guide for you and your parents, P-FLAG, 1995
Stonewall News Northwest, Spokane, WA. 1 issue.
Supporting People With AIDS: The GMHC Model, Gay Men's Health Crisis
Surgeon General's Report on Acquired Immune Deficiency Syndrome
Surgeon General's Report to the American Public on HIV Infection and AIDS(Novello, Koop)
The First Ten Years GMHC, 1990-1991 Annual Report
Why ask Why? Addressing the Research on Homosexuality and Biology, P-FLAG, 1995
Tips and Tactics, 45 issues.
The Truth about Jane (VHS). Hearst Entertainment, 2001.
Understanding AIDS: A Message From The Surgeon General
Anti-Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual and Transgendered Violence in 1997, a report of the National Coalition of Anti-Violence Programs
Income Inflation: the myth of affluence among gay, lesbian, and bisexual Americans, by M.V. Lee Badgett, Ph.D., a joint publication of the Policy Institute of the National Gay and Lesbian Task Force and the Institute for Gay and Lesbian Strategic Studies
Who Decides? A State-by-State Review of Abortion and Reproductive Rights, eighth edition, 1999, National Abortion Rights and Reproductive Rights Action League Foundation
SIECUS Report, vol. 25, no. 4, "Abstinence-only Education"
Your Metro Neighbors, Cincinnati, OH. 2 issues.